<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9"
        xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1">

  <url>
    <loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/assets/montucky-visuals/09_hero_bar_hero.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montucky Moonshine Bar — Helena, Montana Craft Distillery</image:title>
      <image:caption>The Montucky Moonshine bar in Helena, MT — handcrafted spirits and private venue experience in the heart of Big Sky Country.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/assets/montucky-visuals/07_wolf_mystical_large.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montucky Moonshine Wolf — Montana Craft Spirits Brand Art</image:title>
      <image:caption>Mystical wolf artwork representing Montucky Moonshine's wild Montana heritage and handcrafted spirit identity.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/assets/montucky-visuals/01_vintage_poster_hero.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montucky Moonshine Vintage Poster — Buy Montana Moonshine Online</image:title>
      <image:caption>Vintage-style poster art for Montucky Moonshine, Montana's craft moonshine brand inspired by Big Sky Country's bootlegger heritage.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>

  <url>
    <loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/shop</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/assets/montucky-visuals/08_vintage_label_large.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montucky Moonshine Vintage Label — Shop Craft Spirits Helena MT</image:title>
      <image:caption>Montucky Moonshine vintage label design — shop handcrafted Montana moonshine, mugs, tees, and merchandise online.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/assets/montucky-visuals/04_tattoo_skull_medium.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montucky Moonshine Skull Art — Montana Moonshine Merchandise</image:title>
      <image:caption>Bold skull artwork featured on Montucky Moonshine apparel and merchandise — shop tees, hats, and accessories.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>

  <url>
    <loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/venue</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/venue/bar_long.webp</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montucky Moonshine Private Venue Bar — Event Space Helena Montana</image:title>
      <image:caption>The long bar at Montucky Moonshine's private event venue in Helena, MT — available for private parties, corporate events, and distillery experiences.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/venue/lounge.webp</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montucky Moonshine Lounge — Private Event Venue Helena MT</image:title>
      <image:caption>Lounge seating area at Montucky Moonshine's private venue — book a spirits-and-sound experience in Helena, Montana.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/venue/pool_table.webp</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montucky Moonshine Venue Games Area — Book a Montana Event Space</image:title>
      <image:caption>Pool table and games area at Montucky Moonshine's private venue in Helena, Montana. Perfect for private parties and corporate events.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>

  <url>
    <loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/lifestyle</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/assets/montucky-visuals/09_hero_bar_medium.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montucky Moonshine Lifestyle — Montana Outdoor Spirits Culture</image:title>
      <image:caption>Explore the Montucky Moonshine lifestyle: campfire cocktail recipes, Montana history, and outdoor-inspired drinking culture from Big Sky Country.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/assets/montucky-visuals/10_metal_80s_large.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montucky Moonshine 80s Metal Art — Montana Craft Spirits Heritage</image:title>
      <image:caption>Retro metal-inspired artwork celebrating Montucky Moonshine's rebellious heritage — where Montana's bootlegger past meets craft spirits culture.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>

  <url>
    <loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/lifestyle/recipes</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/assets/montucky-visuals/03_psychedelic_medium.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montucky Moonshine Cocktail Recipes — Montana Moonshine Drinks</image:title>
      <image:caption>Explore 18 Montana-inspired moonshine cocktail recipes from Montucky — from campfire hot toddies to huckleberry smashes and Montana Mules.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>

  <url>
    <loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/lifestyle/culture</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/assets/montucky-visuals/02_neon_sign_medium.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montana Moonshine History — Bootleggers, Prohibition, and Craft Spirits</image:title>
      <image:caption>Dive into Montana's rich moonshine history — from Prohibition-era bootleggers like Bertie Brown and Josephine Doody to the modern craft spirits revival.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/assets/montucky-visuals/06_grunge_90s_medium.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montucky Moonshine Culture Art — Montana Craft Spirits Identity</image:title>
      <image:caption>Grunge-inspired artwork reflecting Montucky Moonshine's deep roots in Montana's independent, rebellious spirit culture.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>

  <url>
    <loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/lifestyle/culture/montana-lady-bootleggers</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/assets/montucky-visuals/05_steampunk_medium.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montana Lady Bootleggers — Bertie Brown and Josephine Doody History</image:title>
      <image:caption>The remarkable stories of Montana's women bootleggers during Prohibition — Bertie Brown of Lewistown and Josephine Doody of Glacier Park.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>

  <url>
    <loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/lifestyle/recipes/montana-mule</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/assets/montucky-visuals/07_wolf_mystical_medium.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montana Mule Moonshine Cocktail Recipe — Ginger Beer and Moonshine</image:title>
      <image:caption>The Montana Mule: Montucky Moonshine, ginger beer, and fresh lime in a copper mug — Montana's answer to the classic Moscow Mule.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>

  <url>
    <loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/lifestyle/recipes/huckleberry-moonshine-smash</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/assets/montucky-visuals/08_vintage_label_medium.png</image:loc>
      <image:title>Huckleberry Moonshine Smash Recipe — Montana Wild Huckleberry Cocktail</image:title>
      <image:caption>The Huckleberry Moonshine Smash — a Montana-exclusive cocktail made with wild huckleberries, Montucky Moonshine, and fresh lemon.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>

  <url>
    <loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/about</loc>
    <image:image>
      <image:loc>https://montucky-moonshine-proposal.netlify.app/venue/bar.webp</image:loc>
      <image:title>Montucky Moonshine — Craft Distillery and Private Venue Helena Montana</image:title>
      <image:caption>Montucky Moonshine is a handcrafted spirits brand and private event venue based in Helena, Montana — rooted in Big Sky Country's wild, independent spirit.</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>

</urlset>
